(Elon:)for being too generous
with the gravy.
(chuckles)
(Howard:)Oh, man. I...
What an honor to meet you.
I'm-I'm such a fan
of Tesla and SpaceX.
(Howard:)All your companies.
(Howard:)Howard Wolowitz, Caltech.
(Elon:)Nice to meet you, Howard.
Feels great to come down here
(Elon:)and help the less fortunate,
huh?
(Howard:)Oh, yeah.
(Howard:)Nothing better
than helping people.
(Howard:)Which is something I realized
(Howard:)when I was viewing Earth
(Howard:)from the deck of
the International Space Station,
(Howard:)where I spent two months as
a payload specialist, a job
(Howard:)I was qualified for because
I'm an MIT-trained engineer.
(Elon:)And I thought
I ladled the gravy on thick.
(Howard:)Sorry. It's just...
(Howard:)you're you, you know?
(Howard:)And I really want you
to adopt me.
(Elon:)Well, you're here
on Thanksgiving,